<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<changelog bulletedList="false">
	<changelogversion versionName="0.5.0" changeDate="?? Feb 2015">
		<changelogtext>+ Added spike alert option to Price Change Alarm.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Added Bitspark, Coinbase, Mulcoin, OneWorldCoin and Yunbi exchanges.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Added Chinese, German, Italian, Polish, Portuguese and Spanish translations.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Last price on alarm list is now coloured according to price direction (up, down or same).</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Added arrow to the alarm triggered notification showing which direction the price took.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Added app settings to control volume and dismiss no internet notification.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Icon was completely redesigned.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Rearranged information on the alarms' rows.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Offed alarms are now continuously updated while alarm list is visible.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Updated ANX, Bitcurex, BitMarket.pl, CEX.IO, 796 Exchange and OKCoin pairs.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Fixed bugs in Bitcoin.de, CCEX and Kraken exchanges' interaction.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Fixed bug which triggered alarms with small update intervals repeatedly even after turning them off.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Fixed exchange data fetching on low quality internet connections.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>- Removed Justcoin and Vault of Satoshi exchange.</changelogtext>
	</changelogversion>
	
	<changelogversion versionName="0.4.0" changeDate="17 Oct 2014">
		<changelogtext>+ Added exchanges: BTC100 and BtcTrade.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Added OKCoin futures.</changelogtext>
	</changelogversion>
	
	<changelogversion versionName="0.3.0" changeDate="16 Oct 2014">
		<changelogtext>+ Added exchanges: Atomic Trade, BitBay, Bitcurex, BitMarket.pl, C-CEX, CCEDK, CoinMkt, Coins-E, Crypto-Trade, Cryptonit, Justcoin, Paymium and Vircurex.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Added Czech translation.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Price Change alarms now retry to get last value after failing due to unavailable internet connection.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>- Removed Mintpal exchange (currently offline).</changelogtext>
	</changelogversion>
	
	<changelogversion versionName="0.2.1" changeDate="14 Oct 2014">
		<changelogtext>* Fixed a bug when alarms with default notification were crashing the application.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Fixed a bug where alarms with default silent notification were playing sound.</changelogtext>
	</changelogversion>
	
	<changelogversion versionName="0.2.0" changeDate="13 Oct 2014">
		<changelogtext>+ Added exchanges: ANX, BTC Markets, CampBX, CEX.IO, itBit and LakeBTC.</changelogtext>
	</changelogversion>
	
	<changelogversion versionName="0.1.0" changeDate="10 Oct 2014">
		<changelogtext>+ Added Bitfinex exchange.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Added X symbol to SearchableListPreference to clear the entire search string at once.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Improved Boilr icon.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* RingtonePreference in alarm creation and settings now displaying the correct sound.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>- Removed XMR donation address from the app. Altcoins' addresses are available only on the website.</changelogtext>
	</changelogversion>
	
	<changelogversion versionName="0.0.0" changeDate="7 Oct 2014">
		<changelogtext>First public beta.</changelogtext>
	</changelogversion>
</changelog>