<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<changelog bulletedList="false">
    <changelogversion versionName="0.6.0" changeDate="?? Apr 2015">
        <changelogtext>+ Added button to refresh all alarms.</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>* Fixed bug that allowed re-usage of a previous alarm ID.</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>
	<changelogversion versionName="0.5.0" changeDate="25 Mar 2015">
		<changelogtext>+ Added Banx.io, Basebit, Bit2c, Bitex.la, BitKonan, BitMaszyna, Bitspark, Bitso, BTCExchange, BTCGreece, BTCTurk, Coinbase, CoinMate, Coinsetter, CoinTree, Coinut, CryptoFacilities, Digital Securities Exchange, Jubi, Mercado Bitcoin, Mulcoin, OneWorldCoin, Quadriga CX, Thailand Bitcoin Exchange, The Rock Trading, VirWox, Yobit, Yuanbaohui and Yunbi exchange</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Added Chinese, French, German, Italian, Polish, Portuguese and Spanish translations.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Last price on alarm list is now coloured according to price direction (up or down).</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Added arrow to the alarm triggered notifications showing price direction.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Added app setting to control volume.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ In alarms' list, clicking on alarm's limits or change value opens a dialog for quick editing.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Alarms can now be reordered.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Added undo toast when alarm is deleted.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Added pinstripe background.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Alert type, sound and vibrate can now be switched between an alarm specific value and the app's default.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Added up navigation. Added back navigation when directly entering a deep-level activity.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Icon, alarms' list and alarm triggered notification completely redesigned.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Price Change Alarm now uses a rolling time frame.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Offed alarms are now continuously updated while alarm list is visible.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Dismissing a no internet notification now prevents showing it again until you get a new internet connection.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Updated ANX, Bitcurex, BitMarket.pl, CEX.IO, 796 Exchange and OKCoin pairs.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Fixed bugs in Allcoin, Bitcoin.de, BTC100, CCEX, Huobi and Kraken exchanges' interaction.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Fixed bug which triggered alarms with small update intervals repeatedly even after turning them off.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Fixed exchange data fetching on low quality internet connections.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>- Removed 1BSE, Atomic Trade, CoinMkt, Coin-Swap, Crypto-Trade, Justcoin, MintPal and Vault of Satoshi exchanges.</changelogtext>
	</changelogversion>
	
	<changelogversion versionName="0.4.0" changeDate="17 Oct 2014">
		<changelogtext>+ Added exchanges: BTC100 and BtcTrade.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Added OKCoin futures.</changelogtext>
	</changelogversion>
	
	<changelogversion versionName="0.3.0" changeDate="16 Oct 2014">
		<changelogtext>+ Added exchanges: Atomic Trade, BitBay, Bitcurex, BitMarket.pl, C-CEX, CCEDK, CoinMkt, Coins-E, Crypto-Trade, Cryptonit, Justcoin, Paymium and Vircurex.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Added Czech translation.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Price Change alarms now retry to get last value after failing due to unavailable internet connection.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>- Removed Mintpal exchange (currently offline).</changelogtext>
	</changelogversion>
	
	<changelogversion versionName="0.2.1" changeDate="14 Oct 2014">
		<changelogtext>* Fixed a bug when alarms with default notification were crashing the application.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Fixed a bug where alarms with default silent notification were playing sound.</changelogtext>
	</changelogversion>
	
	<changelogversion versionName="0.2.0" changeDate="13 Oct 2014">
		<changelogtext>+ Added exchanges: ANX, BTC Markets, CampBX, CEX.IO, itBit and LakeBTC.</changelogtext>
	</changelogversion>
	
	<changelogversion versionName="0.1.0" changeDate="10 Oct 2014">
		<changelogtext>+ Added Bitfinex exchange.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>+ Added X symbol to SearchableListPreference to clear the entire search string at once.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* Improved Boilr icon.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>* RingtonePreference in alarm creation and settings now displaying the correct sound.</changelogtext>
		<changelogtext>- Removed XMR donation address from the app. Altcoins' addresses are available only on the website.</changelogtext>
	</changelogversion>
	
	<changelogversion versionName="0.0.0" changeDate="7 Oct 2014">
		<changelogtext>First public beta.</changelogtext>
	</changelogversion>
</changelog>
